Guide to the Leslie Cagan Papers TAM.138
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Subject Files
  - Coalition for a People's Alternative: People's Convention and Democratic National Convention: Press, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Coalition for a People's Alternative: People's Convention, New York, NY: "Declaration of Charlotte Street," Drafts and Publication, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Columbia University: Student Strike, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Cultural Work, Inc.: Correspondence, undated, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Cultural Work, Inc: Holly Near and inti-illimani Tour, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Edelin Trial: Support for Dr. Kenneth Edelin, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - FBI Surveillance, Anti-Repression, Political Prisoners, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Ferry, Carol Bernstein, undated, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Food, Shelter Resource Guides, New York and New Jersey, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Gay, Lesbian, Transsexual Liberation: Literature, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Gay Socialist Group, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Gay Speakers Bureau, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Housing Action Week: Borough Meetings, undated, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Housing Action Week: Events, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Housing Action Week: Food Collection Sites, undated, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Housing Action Week: Listeners Action on Homelessness and Housing, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Housing Action Week: Literature Flyers, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Housing Action Week: Outreach, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Housing Action Week: Press, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Housing Action Week: Rally Logistics, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Housing Action Week: Steering Committee, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Housing Now!, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Hyde Amendment, Petition Campaign to Defeat: Abortion Task Force, People's Alliance, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Hyde Amendment, Petition Campaign to Defeat: Reproductive Rights National Network, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - International Day of Action on Abortion and Sterilization: International Campaign for Abortion Rights, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - International Day of Action on Abortion and Sterilization: Northeast Coalition for Reproductive Rights, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - International Day of Action on Abortion and Sterilization: Northeast Coalition for Reproductive Rights: Outreach, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - International Day of Action on Abortion and Sterilization: Northeast Coalition on Reproductive Rights: Press, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - International Student, Faculty Strike Against the War in Vietnam, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - International Women's Day, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - International Women's Day, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - International Women's Year: National Gay Task Force, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - International Women's Year: National Women's Conference, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - International Women's Year: National Women's Conference: Conference Information and Publications, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - International Women's Year: National Women's Conference: Follow-up, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - International Women's Year: National Women's Conference: Press, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Jobs With Peace, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Just Peace Project, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - King, Dr. Martin Luther, Death of: NYU activities, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Korea: Friends of the Korean People, Korea Report, 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Marxist-Feminist Group: Conferences, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - May 6th Coalition: March on Washington Against Nuclear Power, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Media Accountability Project and Conference, undated, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Mel King Campaign, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Mel King Campaign: Block Party, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Mel King Campaign: Campaign Committee, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Mel King Campaign: Campaign Literature, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Mel King Campaign: Candidates Forum on Central American Foreign Policy, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Mel King Campaign: Committee to Elect Mel King: Advertisements, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Mel King Campaign: Committee to Elect Mel King: Canvass, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Mel King Campaign: Committee to Elect Mel King: Finances, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Mel King Campaign: Correspondence and Memoranda, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Mel King Campaign: Daily Calendar and Schedule, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Mel King Campaign: Field Operations (I), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Mel King Campaign: Field Operations (II), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Mel King Campaign: Field Operations (III), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Mel King Campaign: Field Operations: Memoranda, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Mel King Campaign: Field Operations: Nominating Petitions, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Mel King Campaign: Fundraising, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Mel King Campaign: Fundraising: House Parties, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Mel King Campaign: Get Out The Vote, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Mel King Campaign: Issue Groups, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Mel King Campaign: Jewish Defense League, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Mel King Campaign: Letter Writing Campaign, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Mel King Campaign: Media Committee, Media Plan, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Mel King Campaign: Media Clippings, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mel King Campaign: Organizer's Notebook, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Mel King Campaign: Polling Data, Statistics, Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mel King Campaign: Press Releases, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mel King Campaign: Staff Meetings, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Mel King Campaign: Telephone Lists, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mel King Campaign: Voter Contact, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Mobilization for Justice and Peace in Central America and South Africa (MJPCASA): City Council Resolutions and Endorsements, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - MJPCASA: Civil Disobedience, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - MJPCASA: Congressional Accountability Day, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - MJPCASA: Endorsement Response Forms, undated-1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - MJPCASA: Fenton Communications Inc., Mobilization Press Coverage, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - MJPCASA: Finances, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - MJPCASA: Flyers, Poster Drafts, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - MJPCASA: Follow-up, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - MJPCASA: Funding, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - MJPCASA: Humanitarian Aid, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - MJPCASA: International Endorsements, undated, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - MJPCASA: Jam for Justice, undated, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - MJPCASA: Local Coalitions, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - MJPCASA: Logistics, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - MJPCASA: Media, Press Clippings, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - MJPCASA: New York City Mobilization, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - MJPCASA: Outreach, Organizing Packet, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - MJPCASA: Performers, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - MJPCASA: Program Committee, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - MJPCASA: Right Wing Attack on, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - MJPCASA: Signers of April Mobilization "call", 1987 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - MJPCASA: Staff, Volunteers, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - MJPCASA: Steering Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - MJPCASA: Student Mobilization Committee, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Mobilization for Peace and Justice: Survivalfest, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Mobilization for Survival: International Task Force, World Peace March, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mobilization for Survival: National Organization, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mobilization for Survival: Proposals to National Conference, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Mobilization for Survival: Religious Task Force, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Mobilization for Survival: Strategy, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Mobilization for Survival: Survival Summer, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - National Network of Gay and Lesbian Socialists, undated, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - National Committee for Independent Political Action (NCIPA): Anti-Racism, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - NCIPA: Budget, 1986-1987-1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - NCIPA: Cuba, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - NCIPA: Events, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - NCIPA: Executive and Steering Committee, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - NCIPA: Executive and Steering Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - NCIPA: Executive and Steering Committee, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - NCIPA: Formation of, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - NCIPA: Health Task Force, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - NCIPA: Internal Structure, Bi-laws, Publications, 1986-1989 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - NCIPA: Media, Press Clippings, 1985-1988 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - NCIPA: Outreach, undated, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - NCIPA: Outreach Mailings, 1985-1989 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - NCIPA: Position Papers, undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - NCIPA: Rainbow Coalition, 1984-1989 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - NCIPA: Speakers' Bureau, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - National Lesbian Conference, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - New York University (NYU): Ad Hoc Committee for a Democratic University (I), 1967 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - NYU: Ad Hoc Committee for a Democratic University (II), 1967 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - NYU: Ad Hoc Committee to Oppose a Tuition Increase, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
  - NYU: Dow Chemical Company Protest, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 3-4)
  - NYU: Hatchett, John F: Strike in support, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 5-6)
  - NYU: New Student University, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Our Bodies, Ourselves: Lesbian Chapter Revisions, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - People's Alliance: Boston, MA, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - People's Alliance: Correspondence, undated, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - People's Alliance: Flyers, Literature, undated-1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - People's Alliance: National Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - People's Alliance: New York, NY, undated, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - People's Alliance: Working Papers, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - People's Convention, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund: Case Against FBI Spying, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Radical Women Publications, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Reagan Inauguration: Demonstration Against, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Reagan Inauguration: Demonstration Against: Follow-up, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Red Tape Media Collective: Boston Feminist Radio Network, 1973-1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Redwood Records Cultural and Educational Fund, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Redwood Records Cultural and Educational Fund, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Reproductive Rights National Network (I), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Reproductive Rights National Network (II), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Reproductive Rights National Network, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Reproductive Rights National Network, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Reproductive Rights National Network, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Reproductive Rights National Network: Formation of, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Republican National Convention Protest: Flyers, Literature, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Republican National Convention Protest: Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Republican National Convention Protest: Outreach, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Republican National Convention Protest: Press, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Rock Against Reagan Tour, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "The Second Sex" – Commemorative Conference on Feminist Theory, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Socialist-Feminist Conference, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Socialist-Feminist Group, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Socialist-Feminist Group, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Socialist-Feminist Group, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Socialist-Feminist Group, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - St. Louis Women's Radio Show, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - "Stop US Intervention in Central America and the Caribbean" Rally, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - "Stop US Intervention in Central America and the Caribbean" Rally: Flyers and Press, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Student Mobilization Committee Against the War in Vietnam, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Student Mobilization Committee Against the War in Vietnam: Anti-War Demonstration, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Susan Saxe: Press, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee: Flyers, Posters, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee: Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee: Public Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee: Susan Saxe Poetry, 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee: Susan Saxe Statements, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee: Video Project, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Symbionese Liberation Army: Dragon Supplement, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - United Nations Special Session on Disarmament II (UNSSD II): Affiliated Activities, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - UNSSD II: African-American Executive Committee, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - UNSSD II: Campaign for, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - UNSSD II: Children's March, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - UNSSD II: Civil Disobedience, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - UNSSD II: Contingent Marches, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - UNSSD II: Coordinating Committee, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - UNSSD II: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - UNSSD II: Cultural Task Force, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - UNSSD II: Executive Committee Meetings, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - UNSSD II: Financial Committee, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - UNSSD II: Flyers, Literature, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - UNSSD II: International, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - UNSSD II: International Liaison Office, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - UNSSD II: Logistics, Buses, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - UNSSD II: Logistics, Housing, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - UNSSD II: Logistics, March Route, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - UNSSD II: Logistics, Meetings, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - UNSSD II: Logistics, Peacekeeping, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - UNSSD II: Media Task Force, Press Releases, 1981-1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - UNSSD II: Mobilization For Survival, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - UNSSD II: Mobilization For Survival, Religious Task Force, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - UNSSD II: Mobilization To New York, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - UNSSD II: New York June 12th Disarmament Campaign, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - UNSSD II: Outreach, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - UNSSD II: Post-June 12th Activities, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - UNSSD II: Press Conference, April 19, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - UNSSD II: Press Coverage, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - UNSSD II: Rally Committee, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - UNSSD II: Rally Program, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - UNSSD II: Resumes, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - UNSSD II: Temporary Executive Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - UNSSD II: Thank You and Congratulation Letters, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - UNSSD III: Affiliated Events, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - UNSSD III: Affiliated Organizations, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - UNSSD III: Mobilization for Survival Education Fund, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - UNSSD III: Mobilization for Survival Education Fund: Contracts, Legal Documents, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of, Administrative Committee, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Call to Support, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Civil Disobedience, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Contingent Marches, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Environmental Control Board Violation, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Funding (I), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Funding (II), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Funding, Grants and Foundations, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: International Peace Concert, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: International Peace Conference, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Labor, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Literature, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Loans, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Logistics, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Media, Press, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Outreach, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Outreach mailings, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Outreach, New York City, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Outreach, Received Response Forms (I), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Outreach, Received Response Forms (II), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Outreach, Received Response Forms (III), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Outreach, Received Response Forms (IV), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Outreach, Received Response Forms: Student Mailing List, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Post June 11th, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Speakers, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Staff Meeting, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Stage and Sound Production Costs, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Steering Committee, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - UNSSD III: National Coalition in Support of: Transportation, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - UNSSD III: National Religious Events Coalition, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - UNSSD III: Press Coverage, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - University of Massachusetts, Boston: Faculty and Librarians for a Fair Contract, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Vieques, Puerto Rico: Vieques Support Network, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Vietnam: Literature, 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Weather Underground Organization, undated, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Women and The Law: National Conference, undated, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Women In Vietnam: Conference, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Women's Liberation, undated, 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Women's Union: Chicago Women's Liberation Union, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Women's Union: Twin Cities, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Women's Union: Valley Women's Union, 1972-1975 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - "Yes We Can": Fair and Demonstration, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Series II: Subject Files Accessioned 1993-2014
  - Abortion Action Coalition: Boston, MA, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - AFSC: Middle East Peace Education Program: 2nd Informational Packet, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - AFSC: Middle East Peace Education Program: 3rd Informational Packet, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - AFSC: Middle East Peace Education Program: 4th Informational Packet, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - AFSC: Middle East Peace Education Program: 5th Informational Packet, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - AFSC: Middle East Informational Mailings 1, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - AFSC: Middle East Informational Mailings 2, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Anniversary of Hiroshima and Nagasaki, 1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Anti- Repression: Gabriner, Vicki, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - AAPJJ: Administrative, Personnel, and Steering Committees, 1984-1985, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - AAPJJ: Flyers, Literature, 1985, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - AAPJJ: Follow-Up, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - AAPJJ: Lobby Day, 1985, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - AAPJJ: Logistics, 1985, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - AAPJJ: Mailings, Outreach, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - AAPJJ: Press Clippings, Press Releases, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - "Arms Race vs. Human Needs: A Dialogue on Jobs, Peace, and Justice" Conference, Fisk University, Nashville, TN, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Campaign for a Just Supreme Court, 1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Carthan, Eddie James: Petition campaign for release and exoneration former Mississippi mayor, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Coalition for a People's Alternative, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Culture Work, Inc., Oakland, CA, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Friends of the Earth, 1977, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Grand Jury Procedure, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Housing Action Week, New York, NY, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Housing Action Week, New York, NY: Borough Organizing, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Housing Action Week, New York, NY: Flyers, Literature, 1988, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Housing Action Week, New York, NY: Mailings, Outreach, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Housing Action Week: Press Clippings, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - "Housing Now!": March, Washington, D.C., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - International Women's Year: Conference, Houston, TX, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - "Jesse Jackson '88" Campaign for Presidency: Correspondence, Memoranda, Mailings, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - "Jesse Jackson '88" Campaign for Presidency: Flyers, Literature, 1988, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - "Jesse Jackson '88" Campaign for Presidency: Labor, 1988, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - "Jesse Jackson '88" Campaign for Presidency: National Lavender Stripe, Lesbians and Gays for Jackson, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - "Jesse Jackson '88" Campaign for Presidency: Position Papers, Reports, Speeches, 1987-1988, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - "Jesse Jackson '88" Campaign for Presidency: Press Clippings, Press Releases, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Lucy Parsons Women's Coalition: Boston, MA, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Mel King for Congress Campaign, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Middle East Justice Network, The, 1990, undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Mobilization for Justice and Peace in Central America and South Africa (MJPCASA), 1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - MJPCASA: Budget, Finances, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - MJPCASA: Civil Disobedience, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - MJPCASA: Endorsements, Organizational Affiliates, 1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - MJPCASA: Flyers and Literature, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - MJPCASA: Jam for Justice, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - MJPCASA: Leslie Cagan's Document Originals File, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - MJPCASA: Logistics, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - MJPCASA: Mailings, Outreach, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - MJPCASA: Media: Press Releases: Statements to the Press, 1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - MJPCASA: Press Clippings, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - MJPCASA: Program, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - MFS: 3rd Annual Conference: Louisville, KY, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - MFS: 4th Annual Conference: Pittsburgh, PA, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - MFS: 5th National Conference: Milwaukee, WI, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - MFS: 6th National Conference: Austin, TX, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - MFS: 7th National Conference: Berkeley, CA, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)